pluginsbyigor.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Plugins By Igor

This privacy policy sets out how Vigorous Software Inc. uses and protects any information that you give Vigorous Software Inc. when you use this website.

Vigorous Software Inc. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Vigorous Software Inc. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 1st, 2018.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails **** about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, **** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**OPT-IN NOTICE:** By Participating, You Expressly “Opt In” To Receive Emails from Vigorous Software Inc.  
Disclosures: We may disclose information about you and your use of our Web Site and Services if we believe such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law or legal process; (ii) to protect or defend the rights or property of us or others; (iii) to enforce the Website Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; and (iv) to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. In addition we may share or transfer information about you and that you provide to us, to one or more third party entities pursuant to a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion, or all of, the assets or stock of our company or its affiliated entities, or as otherwise provided herein. We may also disclose information to allow third party business partners and affiliates deliver marketing offers to you.

**Third Party Advertising and Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Web site and other Web sites. In the course of serving advertisements, these companies may place or recognize a unique ‘cookie’ on your hard drive, and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>.

Vigorous Software Inc. shares Web site usage information about visitors to our Web site with a reputable third-party advertising company for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites. For this purpose, we and our third-party advertising company note some of the pages you visit on our Web site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). The information collected by our third-party advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable. For more information about our third-party advertiser, please [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). To opt out of the targeting program, please [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info [at] pluginsbyigor.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 3219 Yonge Str #325, Toronto ON M4N 2L3, Canada

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
